admissions.cn 2016-11-22

# Privacy Policy Study in china & Admissions.cn

Admissions.cn, including its affiliates, is committed to respect your privacy. We do not sell, lease, rent or otherwise disclose your personal data to third parties. This privacy policy details what information is collected and how it is used and applies to visits made through this Website. 

Surfing Data   
When you visit any page on the Website, we use standard web server log files to collect information on the efficiency and working of the Website. This information includes the number of times a web page is accessed, the browser used, paths taken when moving through the Website, and search terms entered by users. We keep this information for an indefinite time to improve the operation of the Website and to prepare anonymous data compilations regarding traffic on the Website. 

Student Login   
When you sign up on Admissions.cn student login, you provide us with your name, email, gender, and birth date ("Personal Information"). You will be able to add a picture of yourself. Once you register you can provide other information about yourself by connecting with, for example, your current city, activities, school size, and other preferences. You can also provide personal information about yourself. 

We also collect and store your personal application information if you voluntarily enter it. This information is forwarded to our consultants and passed on to the schools or services you identify, so that our consultants, the schools, or third party partners may contact you with more information or enable the schools to review your documents before issuing the admission notice and JW202 form to you. In addition, we use this information to match you with schools based on various factors including preferences and scores. We will not share your Personal Information with anyone except as provided in this privacy policy. 

Non-Personal information and Cookies   
When you visit and interact with the Website, we may collect non-personal information such as a catalog of the site pages you visit or your IP address. Admissions.cn does use cookies (small files put on your computer).   
Schools Contacting You   
Different schools and services have different methods of following up with student information requests. Some will send brochures in the mail, while others will reply via email or try to contact individuals by telephone. By using our service to request information from schools or services, you are giving permission to the schools or services (or their partners or vendors) to contact you, using the method of their choice, to fulfill your information request. 

Sharing information on Admissions.cn   
This section explains how your privacy settings work, and how your information is shared on Admissions.cn. You should always consider your privacy settings before sharing information on Admissions.cn. 

Privacy Policy Changes   
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree to this Privacy Policy, and any changes to the same, by visiting this Website. Therefore, we encourage you to review changes to our privacy policy every time you visit this Website.
